[ar: ELISA]
[ti: God only knows]
[al: God only knows ～集積回路の夢旅人/Oratorio The World  god Only Knows]
[by: leaflu]
[offset: 5000]
[length: 08:08]
[id: uovcwwci]
[00:05.58]What I’m seeing……Is it real? /我看到了什麼.....這是真的嗎?
[00:12.75]Chapter 1
[00:12.75]
[00:13.28]What I’m feeling……Is it real? /我感覺到什麼.....這是真的嗎?
[00:20.72]What I’m doing……Is it real? /我正在做什麼.....這是真的嗎?
[00:26.66]There is no regrets, satisfy my curiosities /沒有遺憾,滿足我的好奇心
[00:32.36]There is a new world waiting, explore my possibilities /有一個新世界在等待,探索我的可能性
[00:38.61]There is no guarantee, just improve my abilities /沒有保證,只是改進我的能力
[00:45.36]There is a choice to make, setting the right priorities /有一個抉擇,設定一個正確的優先(選擇)
[00:50.81](You will always be the one, so feel the power /你永遠是唯一一個,所以感覺力量吧
[00:57.94]And you should know the sun comes up – For you) /你應該知道太陽升起 - 為了你>
[01:03.81]There is no regrets, satisfy my curiosities /沒有遺憾,滿足我的好奇心
[01:09.50]There is a new world waiting, explore my possibilities /有一個新世界在等待,探索我的可能性
[01:15.38]There is no guarantee, just improve my abilities /沒有保證,只是改進我的能力
[01:21.50]There is a choice to make, setting the right priorities /有一個抉擇,設定一個正確的優先(選擇)
[01:28.69]
[01:29.94]Chapter 2
[01:44.56]
[01:45.06](What is the best you can do? How can you do?) /<你怎麼做是最好的? 你要如何做?>
[01:57.00]I was sitting and thinking the other day /我坐著邊想著過去的日子
[02:03.06]If I fail, I won’t throw my passion away /如果我失敗了,我將不會丟棄我的情感
[02:09.13]Just ’cause giving up is not the only way /只因為放棄並不是為一的方法
[02:14.98]No matter how it’s gonna be, I’ll try it anyway /無論會發生什麼,我將會試任何方法
[02:26.13]
[02:35.52]Chapter 3
[02:37.34]
[02:37.78]Love is such a sweet illusion (Let’s come together) /愛像是一個甜蜜的幻象 (讓我們在一起)
[02:43.84]Can’t seem to stop my imagination (Goes on forever) /不能停止我的想像 (直到永遠)
[02:49.41]What a ridiculous situation (Another matter) /這是一個多麼荒謬可笑的局勢 (另一回事)
[02:55.09]But I can’t deny, I’m faced with a tricky temptation /但我不能否認,我面對一個狡猾的誘惑
[03:00.34]In the world that keeps on changing /這個世界一直在改變
[03:05.84]Don’t know why my heart is aching /我的心不知道為什麼疼痛
[03:11.16]Gotta handle it, no more hesitation /即刻處理吧,不要再猶豫了
[03:20.53]There can be no turning back /那裡不能回頭
[03:23.41]God only knows /只有神知道
[03:24.34]“My mind is as free as the wind /"我的心跟風一樣自由
[03:27.22]But now what I should do is to fall in love” /但是現在我應該做的就是談戀愛"
[03:30.84]God only knows /只有神知道
[03:31.91]“I don’t need that kind of real things /"我不需要那種真實的東西
[03:34.47]Feels like I’m lost in the labyrinth” /感覺像是我迷失在迷宮裡"
[03:38.03]God only knows /只有神知道
[03:39.28]“There must be the meaning of life /"必有個生命的意義
[03:41.91]Somehow unexpected happenings thrill me” /有意外發生使我動搖"
[03:45.47]God only knows /只有神知道
[03:46.75]“Just believe in myself and my dream /"只需相信我自己和我的夢
[03:49.44]Anyone could be a hero and heroine” /任何人都能成為英雄或女主角"
[03:52.88]God only knows /只有神知道
[03:54.00]“Though it’s not so easy to get through /"雖然這並不容易到達
[03:57.13]Here I am, I’m sure that things will go my way” /我在這裡,我很確定所有的事都會按照我的方法走"
[04:00.31]God only knows /只有神知道
[04:01.50]“My mind is as free as the wind /"我的心跟風一樣自由
[04:04.25]But now what I should do is to fall in love” /但是現在我應該做的就是談戀愛"
[04:07.75]God only knows (Your own happiness, you can find it) /只有神知道 <你可以找到自己擁有的幸福>
[04:08.81]“I don’t need that kind of real things /"我不需要那種真實的東西
[04:11.75]Feels like I’m lost in the labyrinth” /感覺像是我迷失在迷宮裡"
[04:15.19]God only knows (Your infinity, you can feel it) /只有神知道 <你可以感受到你的無限>
[04:16.31]“There must be the meaning of life /"必有個生命的意義
[04:19.31]Somehow unexpected happenings thrill me” /有意外發生使我動搖"
[04:22.56]God only knows (Opportunity, you can take it) /只有神知道 <你可以掌握機會>
[04:24.19]“Just believe in myself and my dream /"只需相信我自己和我的夢
[04:26.38]Anyone could be a hero and heroine” /任何人都能成為英雄或女主角"
[04:29.94]God only knows (Toward the future, you can make it) /只有神知道 <你可以行將到來的未來>
[04:31.06]“Though it’s not so easy to get through /"雖然這並不容易到達
[04:33.94]Here I am, I’m sure that things will go my way” /我在這裡,我很確定所有的事都會按照我的方法走"
[04:37.50]
[04:38.88]Chapter 4
[05:07.14]
[05:07.84](Sailing, you’re sailing away /揚帆,你啟航離去
[05:17.95]And now it’s blowing, breeze will take you away) /現在正是起風的時候,微風將會帶你走遠>
[05:30.64]I feel that my spirits rise /我感受到我的情緒高漲
[05:33.52]I will survive and just stay alive /我將會生存下去
[05:40.14]Enjoy being alone, the isolation is not always so bad /享受一個人,隔絕(外在)並不是那麼糟
[05:49.45]Another day has gone by, every day goes by /又一天過去了,每一天的流逝
[05:54.27]In the sky, there’d be a bridge to a bright tomorrow /在天空,有一個橋梁連接光明的明天
[05:58.89](You will find your treasure and share your pleasure /你將會找到你的寶藏和分享你的快樂
[06:13.20]Let me tell you……) /讓我告訴你
[06:21.27]
[06:22.89]Chapter 5
[06:34.89]
[06:35.14](Just keep your vision, your dream, and your soul alive /只要保持你的理想,你的夢,和你靈魂的存在
[06:52.33]Be as you are, I will always be right by your side) /做你自己,我會一直在你身邊>
[07:11.14]Think about my love and my life /想想我的愛、我的人生
[07:17.64]In an uncertain world, face to face with myself(yeah...) /在渺茫的世界裡,與自己面對面
[07:25.45]Continue to make progress, day by day and step by step(step by step) /持續的進步,一天又一天,一步又一步
[07:32.39]I’ve got a good feeling /我得到一個很好的感覺
[07:35.83]So I’m gonna keep on trying, life will go on..... /所以我決定持續的試,生命將會繼續下去......
[07:43.27]
