[id: uovcwwci]
[length: 05:01]
[by: leaflu]
[al: Life is Like a Boat]
[ti: Life is Like a Boat]
[ar: Rie fu]
[00:00.00]Nobody knows who I really am /沒有人知道我究竟是誰
[00:05.69]I never felt this empty before /我以前從未感覺到如此虛無空蕩
[00:10.31]And if I ever need someone to come along /如果我需要有人來陪伴
[00:15.11]Who's gonna comfort me, and keep me strong /誰會安慰我並讓我更加堅強
[00:20.32]We are all rowing the boat of fate /我們都在命運之湖上蕩舟划槳
[00:24.75]The waves keep on comin' and we can't escape /波浪起伏這而我們無法逃離孤航
[00:29.37]But if we ever get lost on our way /但是假使我們迷失了方向
[00:34.12]The waves would guide you thru another day /波浪將指引著我們穿越另一天的曙光
[00:39.19]遠くで息(いき)をしてる　透明(とうめい)になったみたい /在遙遠的地方呼吸著 仿佛變成了透明一般
[00:48.69]暗闇(くらやみ)に思えたけど　目隠(めかく)しされてただけ /還以為是周遭的黑暗 卻只是被蒙住了雙眼
[00:58.97] 
[01:01.70]祈(いの)りをささげて　新(あたら)しい日(ひ)を待(ま)つ /虔誠地祈禱著 期待新的一天的到來
[01:11.09]鮮(あざ)やかに　光(ひか)る海(うみ) その果(は)てまで /直到閃耀著亮麗光芒的 大海邊際
[01:24.17] 
[01:25.40]Life Is Like A Boat
[01:30.78]演唱: Rie fu
[01:34.50]#LeafLu
[01:36.59]Nobody knows who I really am /沒有人知道我究竟是誰
[01:41.30]Maybe they just don't give a damn /或許他們並不會指責我的荒唐
[01:46.02]But if I ever need someone to come along /但如果我需要有人來陪伴
[01:50.70]I know you would follow me, and keep me strong /我知道你會追隨我並使我堅強
[01:55.71]人(ひと)の心(こころ)はうつりゆく　抜(ぬ)け出(だ)したくなる /想從不斷變遷的人心中掙脫
[02:05.35]つきはまた新(あたら)しい周期(しゅうき)で　舟(ふね)を連(つ)れてく /又一輪陰晴圓缺的月亮 牽引著我向前
[02:18.31]And every time I see your face /每一次我看見你的臉龐
[02:22.73]The oceans heave up to my heart /海洋奮力托起我的心臟
[02:27.70]You make me wanna strain at the oars /你令我在盪槳時感到緊張
[02:32.22]And soon I can see the shore /轉眼我竟看不到岸的彼方
[02:42.79]Ah, I can see the shore ... /啊，我看不到岸的彼方......
[02:52.07]When will I see the shore ... /究竟什麼時候才能看到岸的彼方？
[03:05.19]I want you to know who I really am /我希望你能知道我的真實
[03:09.81]I never thought I'd feel this way towards you /我從未想過我將要追隨著你的方向
[03:14.64]And if you ever need someone to come along /但如果你需要有人來陪伴
[03:19.48]I will follow you, and keep you strong /我將追隨著你並使你堅強
[03:24.30]旅(たび)はまだ続いてく　穏(おだ)やかな日(ひ)も /就算平淡安穩的日子裡 旅行也依然繼續
[03:33.95]つきはまた新(あたら)しい周期(しゅうき)で　舟(ふね)を照(しょう)らし出(だ)す /又一輪陰晴圓缺的月亮 照亮了我的身影
[03:46.93]祈(いの)りをささげて　新(あたら)しい日(ひ)を待(ま)つ /虔誠地祈禱著 期待新的一天到來
[03:56.45]鮮(あざ)やかに　光(ひか)る海(うみ)その果(は)てまで /直到那閃耀著亮麗光芒的 大海邊際
[04:06.14]And every time I see your face /每一次我看見你的臉龐
[04:10.42]The oceans heave up to my heart /海洋奮力托起我的心臟
[04:15.45]You make me wanna strain at the oars /你令我在盪槳時感到緊張
[04:19.97]And soon I can see the shore /轉眼我竟看不到岸的彼方
[04:29.50]運命(うんめい)の船(ふね)を漕(そう)ぎ /盪起命運的小舟
[04:33.89]波(なみ)は次(つき)から次へと私(わたし)たちを襲(おそ)うけど /雖然波浪一波一波地襲來
[04:43.25]それも素敵(すてき)な旅(たび)ね　どれも素敵(すてき)な旅(たび)ね /這次仍是美好而奇妙的旅行 每次都是美好而奇妙的旅行
[04:55.68] 
